American Civil Liberties Union Records: Subgroup 2, Organizational Matters Series, 1947-1995: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 1: Organizational Matters, 1930-1995; 582 boxes
  - Subseries 1E.1: Departments: Executive Directors, 1946-1978; 7 boxes
    - Malin: International Civil Liberties- Miscellaneous, 1956; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Malin: International U.S. Territories, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Malin: International U.S. Territories - Carribean, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - Malin: International U.S. Territories - Pacific, 1960; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - Malin: Miscellaneous - Jury Project, 1956; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Malin: Labor - Internal Practices, 1958; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - Malin: Labor - Picketing, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - Malin: Labor - Miscellaneous, 1952-1959; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 12)
    - Malin: Miscellaneous - Legislative Investigating Procedures, 1953-1958; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 13)
    - Malin: Loyalty/ Security - American Bar Association Report on Communism, 1959; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 14)
    - Malin: Loyalty-Security - Religion, 1960; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 15)
    - Malin: Loyalty/Security - Smith Act, 1951; 1961; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 16)
    - Malin: Loyalty/Security - State Sedition Laws, 1956; 1959; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 17)
    - Malin: Loyalty/Security - Miscellaneous, 1950-1957; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 18)
    - Malin: Mass Communication - Equal Time - Political Candidates, 1955; 1960; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Malin: Mass Communication - Government Regulation, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Malin: Mass Communication - Radio/TV Censorship, 1952; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Malin: Mass Communication - Radio/TV Controversy, 1955-1957; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Malin: Mass Communication - Radio/TV - Programming, 1946; 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Malin: Mass Communication - Radio/TV Miscellaneous, 1952-1960; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Malin: Mass Communications - Reporter's Privilege, 1957-1959; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Malin: Miscellaneous Speeches, 1955-1960; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Malin: Passports - Freedom of Movement, 1951-1955; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Malin: Police Practices - Wiretapping, 1961; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - Malin: Police Practices - Miscellaneous, 1954-1961; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - Malin: Miscellaneous - Political Expenditures and Control, 1952; 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - Malin: Miscellaneous - Politics, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Malin: Miscellaneous - Senate Filibuster, 1956-1958; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Malin: Voting Rights - Miscellaneous, 1961; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Malin: Women's Rights - Miscellaneous, 1962; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Malin: Miscellaneous, 1955-1956; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Pemberton: "Human Rights and the Press", 1963; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Pemberton: "Public Health and Individual Liberties", 1963; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Pemberton: Bucknell Conference, 1965; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Pemberton: Miscellaneous, 1964; 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 210, Folder 9-10)
    - Pemberton: Correspondence, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 11)
    - Pemberton: Working Group for Guaranteed Income, 1967; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 12)
    - Pemberton: Letters Signed, 1968; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 13)
    - Pemberton: Clauson, Bart, 1969; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 14)
    - Pemberton: Correspondence, 1969; 2 folders (Box 210, Folder 15-16)
    - Pemberton: Correspondence with Roger Baldwin, 1969; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Pemberton: Correspondence, 1970; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Pemberton: Speeches and Addresses, 1970; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Neier: Miscellaneous, 1970; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Neier: Correspondence, 1971; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Neier: Opposition to Rehnquist Nomination - Senate Response, 1971; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Neier: Correspondence, 1972-1974; 4 folders (Box 211, Folder 7-10)
    - Neier: Miscellaneous, 1978; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 1E.2: Departments: Executive Director Aryeh Neier, 1968-1978; 38 boxes
    Aryeh Neier served as National Executive Director of the ACLU from 1970 to 1978, a time of rapid expansion for the organization. He first joined the ACLU in 1963 and was director of the New York state affiliate for six years, though these files cover only his years as the National Executive Director of the ACLU. These records document the enormous expansion of, and the controversies surrounding, the ACLU in the 1970s and the concomitant financial crisis that led Neier to resign his post in 1978.
    These records (15.96 linear feet) are divided into three subgroups: administrative files, correspondence, and state affiliate files. The administrative files, arranged alphabetically by subject and chronologically within each folder, contain numerous internal memoranda and correspondence concerning the ACLU's involvement in various legal and social issues, including the ACLU's support of the right of Nazis to parade through the predominantly Jewish Chicago suburb of Skokie, Illinois; the ACLU's support for President Nixon's impeachment; and the discovery of the ACLU's investigation of Judge Irving Kaufman, who had presided over the Julius and Ethel Rosenberg espionage trial. Other topics documented in these files include the campaign spending, Equal Rights Amendment, gun control, correspondence to Neier dealing with Civil Liberties Review, privacy legislation, the Rights of... book series, and the growing number of ACLU Foundation projects.
    The correspondence contains letters from members concerning various ACLU issues and donations, spanning the years 1976-1978 arranged chronologically. Carbon copies of Neier's response to most of these letters are included in these files. The state affiliate files, arranged alphabetically by state and chronologically within each folder, contains Neier's correspondence with the leaders of the ACLU state and local branches discussing requests by the branches for increased funding or suggestions for potential cases for the national organization to pursue.
    - Abortion, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Abrams, Morris, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Academic Division, 1977; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Academy of Political and Social Sciences, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Academy for Contemporary Problems, 1974; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Access to the Courts, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Activity Report: ACLU, 1976; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Advertising Council, 1976; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Advocates for Juvenile Justice, 1978; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - ACLU Observer Instructions, undated; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - Aetna Life and Casualty, 1977; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - Affirmative Action, 1973; 1977; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 13)
    - Age Discrimination, 1976; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 14)
    - Agee, Philip, 1977; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 15)
    - Agnew, Spiro, 1973; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 16)
    - Airport Searches, 1973; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 17)
    - Alabama Prison Decision, 1976; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 18)
    - Aliens, 1975; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 19)
    - Alliance for Shaping Safer Cities, 1976; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 20)
    - American Association of Retired Persons, 1977; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 21)
    - American Bar Association, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 22)
    - American Broadcasting Association, 1978; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 23)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 24)
    - American Institute for Marxist Studies, 1977; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 25)
    - American Institute for Public Service, 1974; 1976; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 26)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 27)
    - American Management Association, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 28)
    - American Psychiatric Association, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 29)
    - American Revolution Bicentennial, 1972-1975; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 30)
    - American Society for Information on Science, 1976; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 31)
    - American Telephone and Telegraph, 1972-1977; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Americans United for Separation of Church and State, 1977; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Amicus Briefs, 1974; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Amnesty Project, 1970-1976; 6 folders (Box 213, Folder 4-9)
    - Amsterdam, Tony, 1973; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 10)
    - Anagnos, Aris, 1976; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 11)
    - Angola, 1976; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 12)
    - Anti-ACLU, 1974; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 13)
    - Anti-Defamation League, 1977; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 14)
    - Armour v. Nix, 1975; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 15)
    - Arabs, Liberties of, 1972; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 16)
    - Arrest Records, 1972-1976; 2 folders (Box 213, Folder 17-18)
    - Askin, Frank, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 19)
    - Associate Legal Director, 1978; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 20)
    - Association of American Publishers (AAP), 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 21)
    - Armed Services Vocational Aptitude Battery, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Association of Community Organization for Return Now (ACORN), 1977; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Atmore, Holman, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Atlanta Metro School Case, 1975; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Attorneys' Fees, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Asher, Thomas, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Aust, Vida, 1976; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - Avon Books, 1974-1978; 4 folders (Box 214, Folder 8-11)
    - Baird, William, 1973; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - Bakke v. University of California, 1977-1978; 2 folders (Box 214, Folder 13-14)
    - Baldwin, Roger, 1972-1977; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 15)
    - Baldwin, Roger - Memoirs, 1976; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 16)
    - Bartley v. Kremens, 1975; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 17)
    - Bauer, Diane, 1975; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 18)
    - Beacon Press, 1975; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 19)
    - Bear, Julius, 1977; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 20)
    - Beasley, Joseph, 1974; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Beichman, Arnold, 1976; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Bell, Griffin, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Bell, Griffin - Documentation, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Bell, Griffin - Reports on (Larson), 1977; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Bellush, Jewel, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Benton, Charles, 1978; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - Berg, Vernon, 1976; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - Bergman, Bernard, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 9)
    - Berlin, Gerald, 1975; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 10)
    - Berman, Harriet Katz, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 11)
    - Bernstein, Robert, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 12)
    - Best Products Foundation, 1978; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 13)
    - Bicentennial Conference on United States Constitution, 1976; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 14)
    - Biennial Conference, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 15)
    - Biennial Conference - ACLU, 1978; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 16)
    - Biography of Aryeh Neier, undated; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 17)
    - Biomedical Research, 1977; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 18)
    - U.S. v. City of Blackjack, MO, 1976; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 19)
    - Black Perspectives on the News, 1977; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 20)
    - Bloom and Gelb, 1978; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 21)
    - Board of Directors, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 22)
    - Board of Education, New York City, 1975; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 23)
    - Board Elections, 1976; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 24)
    - Boggan, E.C., 1977; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 25)
    - Book Club - ACLU, 1975; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 26)
    - Border Searches, 1977; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 27)
    - Bork, Robert, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 28)
    - Brando, Marlon - Case, 1973; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 29)
    - Brown, Ralph, Jr, 1978; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 30)
    - Brown, Wood, Ivey, Mitchell and Petty, 1978; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 31)
    - Buchwald, Art, 1977; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 32)
    - Buckley, James L, 1978; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 33)
    - Buckley Amendment, 1976; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 34)
    - Buckley, William F, 1971-1975; 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 35)
    - Budget, 1973-1977; 5 folders (Box 216, Folder 1-5)
    - Busing, 1973; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - Buffalo Law School - Mental Health Symposium, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - Burger, Eastland, Rodino, 1977; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 8)
    - Burger Court, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 9)
    - Cable TV, 1977; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - Califano, Joseph, 1977; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 11)
    - California Attorneys for Criminal Justice, 1976; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 12)
    - Canadian Federation of Civil Liberties, 1972; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 13)
    - Callen, Earl, 1974; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 14)
    - Cambodia, 1973; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 15)
    - Campaign Finances - Correspondence, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 16)
    - Campaign Finances - Clippings, 1976; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 17)
    - Campaign Finances - Testimony, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 216, Folder 18)
    - Campaign Spending - Correspondence, 1971-1975; 1 folder (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Spending - Correspondence, 1976; 1 folder (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - Capital Punishment - Draft Proposals, undated; 1 folder (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - Capital Punishment - Project, 1972-1976; 2 folders (Box 217, Folder 4-5)
    - Capital Punishment, 1973; 1 folder (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - Capital Punishment Project, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - Card Counter Case - Estes v. State of Nevada, 1978; 1 folder (Box 217, Folder 8)
    - Carliner, David, 1973-1978; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1975; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - Canadian Federation of Civil Liberties and Human Rights Association, 1977; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - Carter Administration and Civil Rights, 1978; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 4)
    - Carter, Jimmy, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 5)
    - Castner, Lynn S, 1977; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - Ce Htaw Drug Case, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 7)
    - Censorship, Conference on, 1976; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 8)
    - Census Records, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 9)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1974; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 10)
    - Center for National Security Studies, 1974; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 11)
    - Center for Policy Research, 1976; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 12)
    - Center for Population and Family Health, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 13)
    - Center for Probation Studies, 1976; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 14)
    - CIA, 1976-1977; 2 folders (Box 218, Folder 15-16)
    - CIA: Manuscripts and Depositions, 1976; 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 17)
    - Church/State Issues: Correspondence, 1978; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - Central Conference on Rabbis, 1978; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - Chairman's Committee, 1978; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - Charter Questionnaire, 1975; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - Chavez, Cesar, 1968-1973; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - Child Advocacy Project: Georgia CLU, 1975; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - Child Pornography Act, 1977; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - Child's Right to Parents Project, 1974; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - Children's Defense Fund, 1976; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 9)
    - Children's Rights, 1974; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - Chile, 1974; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 11)
    - Church, Frank, 1975; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 12)
    - Cincinnati Newspaper Case, 1978; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 13)
    - Citizen's Committee on Population and the American Future, 1972; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 14)
    - Citizens for Humanity in Mental Health, 1976; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 15)
    - Civil Liberties Legal Defense Fund, 1975; 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 16)
    - Civil Liberties Review- Correspondence, 1972-1975; 4 folders (Box 219, Folder 17-20)
    - Civil Liberties Review: Correspondence, 1976-1978; 3 folders (Box 220, Folder 1-3)
    - Civil Liberties Review: Proposal, 1975; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - Civil Liberties Review: Subscriptions, 1977; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - Clark, Ramsey, 1972-1976; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - Classified Information - Testimony, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - Clawson, Eldon, 1974; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 8)
    - Cloudy and Neier, 1978; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 9)
    - Code Authority, 1978; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 10)
    - Cohen, Carl, 1978; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 11)
    - Cohen, Jerold, 1975; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 12)
    - Cointelpro, 1975; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 13)
    - Coleman, Mary, 1974; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 14)
    - Colwell, Mary Anna, 1978; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 15)
    - Commager, Henry, 1972; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 16)
    - Committee for Public Advocacy, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 17)
    - Committee for Public Justice (CPJ), 1974-1975; 2 folders (Box 220, Folder 18-19)
    - Committee for Public Justice (CPJ), 1976-1978; 3 folders (Box 221, Folder 1-3)
    - CPJ - Burger Court Conference, 1976; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - Committee for Public Justice and CIA, 1976; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - Committee for Public Justice and FBI, 1976; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - CPJ - FBI Proposals, 1976; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 7)
    - CPJ: Fundraising and Foundations, 1976; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 8)
    - CPJ Forum: "Informants: How Dangerous to Democracy", undated; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 9)
    - CPJ Projects, 1976; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 10)
    - CPJ Testimony: Calamaro-Congressional Oversight, 1976; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 11)
    - Committee for the Defense of Soviet Political Prisoners, 1974; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 12)
    - Committee on the Judiciary - Senate, 1974; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 13)
    - Common Cause, 1976; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 14)
    - Commonwealth Club of California, 1975; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 15)
    - Communications Media Center, 1978; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 16)
    - Community Reform Temple, 1978; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 17)
    - Connecticut Prisoners Rights Project, 1973; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 18)
    - Conservatorship Law, 1977; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 19)
    - Constitutional Conventions, 1973; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 20)
    - Constitution Committee- ACLU, 1976; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 21)
    - Cooper, Claire, 1971-1975; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 22)
    - Cornell University, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 23)
    - Council for Exceptional Children, 1976; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 24)
    - Council for Public Interest in Law, 1976; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 25)
    - Council on Legal Education Opportunity, 1977; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 26)
    - Culver, Thomas, 1972; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 27)
    - Countryman, Vern, 1977; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 28)
    - Cranberg, Gilbert, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 29)
    - Cranston, Alan, 1975; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 30)
    - Craver, Matthews, Smith and Co, 1978; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 31)
    - Credit Cards, 1975; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 32)
    - Crime Victims, 1977; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 33)
    - Crisis [magazine], 1975; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - Cross, Arthur, 1977; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - Cruelty to Animals, 1976; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Dartmouth College, 1975; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - Davis, Ivy, 1976; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - Dees, Morris, 1978; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - Dellums and Powell, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - Dembitz, Nanette, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 8)
    - Demonstrations, 1976; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 9)
    - Department of Defense, 1977; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - Department of State, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 11)
    - Deprogramming, Religious, 1977; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 12)
    - Derian, Pat, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 13)
    - Desegregation, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 14)
    - Desegregation Job Opening, 1977; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 15)
    - Deveaux, Clinton, 1978; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 16)
    - Development Committee, 1978; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 17)
    - Dodd, Christopher J, 1977; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 18)
    - Donaldsen, Kenneth, 1977; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 19)
    - Donner, Frank, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 20)
    - Department of Justice, 1977; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 21)
    - Dorsen, Norman, 1972-1978; 2 folders (Box 222, Folder 22-23)
    - Douglas, William O, 1975; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 24)
    - Drugs, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 25)
    - Due Process for Executive Staff Dismissals, undated; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 26)
    - Dum-Dum (Hollow Point) Bullets, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 27)
    - Dunbar, Leslie, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 28)
    - Dunn, Robert, 1977; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 29)
    - Edelman, Ben, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 30)
    - Eden, Morton, 1977; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 31)
    - Edwards, Donald, 1975; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 32)
    - [U.S.] Elections: Debate, 1976; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 33)
    - Elderly Rights, 1977; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 34)
    - Ellsberg Break-In, 1973; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 35)
    - Elwell, John, 1976; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 36)
    - Energy Crisis, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 37)
    - Ennis, Edward, 1972-1978; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (ERA), 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - ERA-Steering Committee, 1977; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - Equal Time for Candidates, 1976; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 4)
    - Erskine, Hazel, 1974; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 5)
    - Ethical Culture Society, 1977; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 6)
    - Evans, Alice, 1977; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 7)
    - Ex Parte Relations, 1977; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 8)
    - Executive Director Search, 1978; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 9)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1972-1978; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 10)
    - Flag Desecration, 1974; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 11)
    - Flynn, Elizabeth, 1976; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 12)
    - Flynt, Larry, 1978; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 13)
    - Forstat, Cliff, 1976; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 14)
    - Foster Care System, 1974; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 15)
    - Founding Church of Scientology, 1977; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 16)
    - Frankel, Marvin, 1978; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 17)
    - Fraenkel, Osmond, 1973; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 18)
    - Franklin, Bruce v. Stanford University, undated; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 19)
    - Free Speech Association Committee, 1976; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 20)
    - Freedman, Monroe, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 21)
    - Fair Ballot Access Committee, 1977; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 22)
    - Field Development, 1976; 1 folder (Box 223, Folder 23)